pipl.com 2018-11-30

# Privacy Policy

Pipl was built with both its usefulness and your privacy in mind. This policy describes the types of personal information we may collect from our users and how we may use such information. Please note that this policy is not relevant in any way to public information about you or other people that is found on the web and subsequently available on our site. If you'd like to control or remove such information please click here to learn how. 

By using Pipl, you agree to the collection and use of your personal information as described in this policy as well as to Pipl's terms of service. Any significant changes to this policy – will be posted on Pipl's website (www.pipl.com)

**Commitment to Children's Privacy**  
We are committed to protecting the privacy of the very young. To comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, at this time, Pipl is only available to users who are at least 13 years old. If you are under 13, please do not use Pipl's service. 

**Usage information remains private**   
We may collect information about your use of Pipl, such as how often and for how long you are logged on, your search history and other information related to your use of Pipl services. We use this information internally to improve our service, but we will never publish this data nor give it to a third party. 

**Cookies**  
Pipl may use cookies in an effort to improve the quality of our services.   
A cookie is a small data file that is sent to your computer when you first visit a website. Cookies usually include an identification number that is unique to the computer you are using. Such identifier can help us better understand our users and how they are using the website and the services.   
Cookies can improve the quality of service e.g. recognizing a user when he visits the site, displaying the site according to the user’s chosen user settings for language, and maintaining the security of the user’s account. If you prefer, however, you can reset your browser so that it refuses all cookies, or notifies you when a cookie is being sent. 

**Third party websites and services**  
Pipl's services contain links to third party websites and embedded elements from third party web services such as Google Maps; likewise, your query information might be relayed to third party data feeds for additional results. If you use Pipl’s services or follow link to third party websites, some information about you and your query will be visible to subsequent services. Even if the third party website or service is affiliated with us, we have no control over linked sites, services or data feeds, each of which has separate privacy and data collection practices independent of Pipl. As such, we are not responsible for, nor have any control over, the content or the privacy policies of those third party websites or service, and encourage all users to read the privacy policies of each and every website linked from or embedded in pipl.com. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Pipl. 

**Service Providers**  
Our Support Portal is powered by [Kayako](http://www.kayako.com/), please note that when you send us a support request, a feedback, or when you are using the support portal you agree to their policy in addition to ours, we recommend that you read their privacy page for more information. 

**Advertising and partnerships**  
Pipl may display targeted ads and other relevant information, when you are using Pipl's service. Information that relates to a specific advertising campaign or partnership plan will be provided to advertisers and partners only in an aggregate form, no personal information about the person who viewed an ad or used the service will be provided. 

**Disclaimer**   
We reserves the right to disclose information to third parties if we believe we are required to do so by law or have a good-faith belief that such access or disclosure is reasonably necessary to:  
* Satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request;  
* Enforce Pipl's Terms of Use, including investigation of potential violations thereof;  
* Detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues   
* Respond to user support requests;   
* Protect the rights, property or safety of Pipl, its users and the public. 

**Transfer of information**  
Information collected by Pipl may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Pipl or its agents maintain facilities. By using Pipl, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. With respect to the Personal Data that Pipl receives in the United States from its EU-based Customers, Pipl complies with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework, please click here for the Privacy Shield Notice.  
We reserve the right to transfer information in the event of a transfer of ownership of Pipl, such as acquisition by or merger with another company.
